麦克斯  那台车都在外面停一周了
Max, that car has been parked outside for a week now.
你觉得他们在贩毒吗
Do you think they're selling drugs?
我应该这么说
Let me rephrase that.
他们是在贩毒给你吗
Are they selling drugs to you?
不是  他们也不是来跟我买的
No. They're not buying, either.
你们好  我们有全新的摩卡奇诺小蛋糕
Hi. We have a new mochaccino cupcake.
不  别走  那车跟我们无关
Oh, no. No, no, no. That car's not with us.
这是第三次有客人  因为那台放饶舌音乐的车
Well, that's the third customer that didn't stop
而直接走掉了
because of that rap car.
老实说这车没来之前  咱们这里也不是
To be fair, this place wasn't Walmart on Black Friday
人挤人的大卖场啊
before the car showed up.
-我要去叫他挪下地方  -有种
- I'm gonna go ask it to move. - Cool.
我会告诉你的马你死得勇敢
I'll tell your horse you died brave.
虽然死因很白痴  但勇敢
Stupid, but brave.
起码也带上这锅
At least take this pan,
挡住你最不想被[枪]射的部位
and cover the part you wanna get shot in the least.
您好  能跟您聊两句吗
Hi. Can I talk to you for a second?
你的脑袋不许离开我的视线范围内
I need to see your head at all times.
首先
First of all,
人家觉得我超正的
they're obsessed with me.
第二
Second of all,
姐成功搞定了
I handled it.
我不会中枪了吧
Have I been shot?
我成功了  我拯救了这一带
Well, I did it. I saved the neighborhood.
你就是让人把车拖走
You had a car towed.
你又不是把那件破寝具用品店给烧了
You didn't burn down the Bed Bath & Beyond.
不会是那辆车窗黑色  车身蓝色的车吧
It wasn't the blue one with the tinted windows,
又名杀手车
aka, the murder car?
就是又名"杀手车"的那辆车
Aka, the murder car?
告诉我那只是车子车型的别名
Tell me that's the name of the make and model,
像是"丰田杀手款"
like, "The Toyota Murder""
你确定那款不是"本田捅人款"车型吗
Are you sure you're not thinking of the Honda Stabbing?
卡洛琳有个男的来找你
Caroline, some guy stopped by asking for you
他头戴节日头巾  脸上还有泪滴刺青
with a festive bandana and a teardrop tattoo.
节日头巾  还有泪滴刺青
A festive bandana and a teardrop tattoo--
你确定那不是我妈吗
are you sure it wasn't my mother?
他说他想跟你谈谈他车子的事
He said he wanted to talk to you about his car,
所以我把你手机号给他了
so I gave him your number.
-你不是吧  -我以为他是你朋友嘛
- Han! - I thought he was your friend.
我才没有身上有刺青的朋友
I don't have friends with tattoos.
我的朋友甚至连头发都不能有分叉  好吗
I don't even have friends with split ends.
你把我的手机号给了陌生人
You gave a stranger my number.
不止手机号  还有电邮和地址
Your number, your E-mail, and your address.
干嘛  你是大忙人
What? You're a busy girl.
我不知道他用哪种方法才能联系上你嘛
I didn't know the best way for him to reach you.
天啊  麦克斯  我是不是摊上事了
Oh, my God. Max, am I in trouble?
上菜  死肉一团
Pick-up, dead meat.
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
意思就是叫人拖走车窗全黑的车
It means it's never a good idea to have
从来都不是个好主意
a car with tinted windows towed.
这不是天字第一号规矩吗
That's rule number one.
我以为天字第一号规矩是
I thought rule number one was,
"女生擦屁屁  要从前往后"
"always wipe front to back."
-麦克斯  我好担心啊  -我也是
- Max, I'm worried. - Me too.
我一直以为是从后往前擦
I thought it was back to front.
你好吗  纳·京·酷哥
What's up, Nat King Cool?
我老妈是犹太人的好兄弟
And, my brother from a Jewish mother.
我刚抽完一发的老爹
Hey, my daddy that just smoked a fatty.
你看  麦克斯  你男友来了
Oh, look, Max, it's your boyfriend.
他不是我男友  我们就亲热过而已
He's not my boyfriend. We just made out.
我整天都有跟别人玩亲热
I make out with people all the time.
我上周还跟餐厅里的男的亲热呢
I made out with a guy in the diner last week.
那才不是亲热
That wasn't making out.
他是噎着了  你给他做人工呼吸
He was choking, and you gave him mouth-to-mouth.
但后来就开房了  走开啦
Yeah, but it led to sex. Go away.
麦克斯  我来问你点事
Hey, Max, I came in to ask you something.
这对巨乳是纯天然的  常害我腰酸背疼
They're natural, and they hurt my back.
我也想知道
I also wanted to know
明晚要不要一起出去
If you want to hang tomorrow night.
我们可以一起裸上身看电视
We could watch TV with our shirts off.
看看吧
Maybe.
如果你愿意献身  我就请你吃晚饭
And I'll buy you some dinner if you put out.
所以算是约会吗
Ooh, so like a date.
太爽了
Great.
我一般只收5块
I usually charge $5.
你大老远跑来就是想约我出去吗
You came all the way here to ask me out?
我这人比较老派
I'm old-fashioned.
还有就是我手机掉马桶里了
Plus, I dropped my phone in the toilet.
-明天见  -好
- See ya tomorrow. - Okay.
走开啦  人家还要偷懒不干活呢
Now go. I have a job to not do.
-好啦  -快走啦  白痴
- Okay. - Go, idiot.
走就走  你个傻瓜
Okay, dummy.
阿憨  我手没劲了  撑不住你了
Okay, Han, I can't hold you up anymore.
麦克斯  我好像看到杀手车
Max, I think I just saw the murder car go by,
从我们浴室窗子外经过
out the bathroom window.
你实际上看到了什么
What exactly did you see?
一台车
A car.
我是认真的  我觉得他跟踪我回家
No, seriously, I think it followed me home.
三年前  你也"跟着"我回家啊
Well, three years ago, you followed me home,
所以互不赊欠
so we're even.
去吃吧  南茜
There you go, Nancy.
好  我要出门约会去了
Okay, I'm off on my date.
你不能就这么丢下我
You can't leave me here alone.
外面有杀手车在蹲点杀我呢
There's a murder car out there.
别吓唬自己  没人要追杀你
Relax. No one is after you.
是吗
Oh, really?
那我们回家路上听到的那声
What about the person who yelled,
"罩子放亮点  贱人"  那人又是啥意思
"watch yo back, bitch" when we were walking home?
那是我对女童军喊的
That was me, to that girl scout.
她们卖饼干时敢说有薄荷味[大麻]饼干
If you tell someone you're carrying thin mints,
最好保证是真的有大麻饼干
you best be carrying thin mints.
麦克斯  你今晚会回来的吧
Max, you're coming back tonight, right?
我真的有点怕
I'm kind of afraid.
我从来自己晚上一个人在家里待着
I've never been here alone at night.
你不想一个人的话  为什么不打给阿憨
If you don't want to be alone, why don't you call Han?
笑死人了
Very funny.
我打过了  他没空
I did. Han's busy.
他要在"第二人生"里赴乡村方块舞之约
He's going to a country square dance on Second Life.
这是一款网游
It's an online game,
但他说那更像是一种生活方式
but he says it's more of a lifestyle.
他现实第一人生都玩不转了
Don't you have to have a first life
还敢学人玩第二人生
to have a second life?
麦克斯  求你别走
Max, please stay.
打给迪克取消约会
Call Deke and cancel,
不然你回家可能会看到我倒卧血池之中
or else you might come home to find me in a pool of blood.
我一直想要有个池子呢
Oh, I always wanted a pool.
-惨了  是他们要来杀我了  -不可能
- Oh, no, it's them, here to kill me. - It couldn't be.
我还没跟他们结清全款呢
I haven't paid them all the money yet.
姑娘们
Oh, hi, girls.
我刚从牙医那边回来
You know, I just came from the dentist's office.
你们知道迈克·杰克逊死了吗
Did you know that Michael Jackson died?
还有法拉·弗西也死了吗
Oh, and Farrah Fawcett too?
不是吧  我得坐下来缓缓
Oh, no, I've got to sit down.
既然你都来了
Well, since you're here,
你想留下来过个闺蜜之夜吗
do you want to stay and have a girls' night?
听起来很不错
Oh, that's sounds like fun.
就我跟你而已  麦克斯得去约会
It's just me and you. Max has a date.
其实是卡洛琳害怕独处
And Caroline's afraid to be alone.
如果你害怕独处
Well, if you don't want to be alone,
那你为啥平常还表现出一副作女样
then why do you act the way you do?
我要去见迪克了
I got to go meet Deke.
我们要喝到酩酊大醉
We are going out to get wasted,
最好是醉到能往对方鞋子上呕吐那样
hopefully to the point of blowing chunks on each other's shoes.
请别把它想象得跟字面上那么浪漫
But imagine it a little less romantic than it sounds.
卡洛琳  就剩我和你了
Well, Caroline, it's just me and you.
对啊  我觉得会挺好...
I know. I thought it'd be fun if--
我们尽力了
Well, we tried.
晚安
Good night.
别走啊
Don't go.
有危险人物盯上我了
Dangerous people are after me.
在我们波兰  哥萨克人来袭的时候
You know, in Poland, when the Cossacks came,
我们会煮一大锅热水
we would boil water
然后往他们脸上泼
and then throw it in their faces
然后熬汤喝
and then make soup.
好了  晚安  等等
Anyway, have a good one. Wait.
谁啊
Hello?
萝拉  是的
Rula? Yes.
不忙  我今晚超级无敌闲
No, I have absolutely nothing to do tonight.
南茜  看来今晚我们只有彼此了
Well, Nancy, looks like it's just you and me.
我和你  再加上这本2009年的杂志
Yep, you and me and this magazine from 2009.
2009年
Ah, 2009--
那是我当白富美的最后一年
the last year I had anything.
来看看  南茜
Let's see, Nancy.
来看看里面写了什么
What are we gonna read here?
"纽约犯罪率达到历史新高"
"New York city more dangerous than ever."
够了  不看这破玩意了
Okay, that's it. We're done.
只是普通按喇叭吧
That's just a horn, right?
还是这是什么信号
Or is it a signal?
南茜  不是看不起你
No offense, Nancy,
但这情况我们真的很需要一条狗
but we really need a dog in this situation.
你猜怎么着
Oh, guess what.
这里正好是我的地盘呢
We happen to be in my neighborhood.
你泡妞可真有一套
Oh, you are smooth.
你明摆着硬拉我来这一带
Also, you aggressively steered me here
经过杂货店时还进去给我买了保险套
and stopped at a bodega to buy me condoms.
你想要跟我回家  然后...
So you want to come back to my place, and...
捅了个洞洞吗[棕鸡棕牛]
Brown chicken brown cow?
捅了个什么来着
Brown chicken what?
本来不是"啪了个啪啪"吗  我改编成
You know, "bowm chica wowm wowm," but I made it...
捅了个洞洞嘛
brown chicken, brown cow.
所以你脑海里想到这个哏
So you thought of that in your head,
然后自认为"没事  可以说给她听"吗
and your brain was like, "That's okay to say"?
没  我的脑子在想"千万别说
No, my brain was like, "don't say it,
绝对别说  千万别说"
don't say it, don't say it, don't say it"
然后又变成想
And then it was...
捅了个洞洞
Brown chicken, brown cow.
我家到了
Well, this is me.
你想我说什么
What do you want me to say--
"恭喜你  你住大楼里吗"
"Congratulations. You live in a building"?
那样多逊啊  我不住楼里
No, that would be lame. I don't live in a building.
我住这里
I live here.
哪里  我就看到一个垃圾箱
Where? All I see is a dumpster.
对啊  那就是我的公寓
Yeah, it's my apartment.
我把它改装了然后住里面
I converted it, and I live inside.
完全绿色哦
It's totally green.
不是环保的那种绿色
I mean, it's horrible for the environment,
是外边油漆是绿色的
but it's the color green.
你真不是在开玩笑啊
Oh, you're not kidding.
你真的住垃圾箱里吗
You live in a dumpster?
通常跟我回来的女生都是在这环节
This is usually the part where the girl says
说她得回家  明早得早起
she has to be up early tomorrow
或者打电话报警
or call the police.
-所以你也要走了吗  -对啊
- So do you have to go? - Yeah.
我要走进这屌爆的垃圾箱啊
I have to go inside the freakin' cool dumpster.
更屌的还在后头  你看
And if you think it's cool now, watch this.
我的垃圾箱是"越变越大"  不是"乍看挺大"
My dumpster's a grower, not a shower.
我靠  太赞了
Holy crap. This is amazing.
你这里面还有水槽跟炉灶
You have a sink in here and a stove.
这里面是有暖气  还是你教了老鼠
Is it heated in here, or did you teach the rats
怎么铲煤进蒸汽机里
to shovel coal into the engine?
没错  还有屋顶上的太阳能板
Yes, but there's also solar panels on the roof.
还有微波炉呢
And a microwave
这里还有马桶呢
and a bathroom right here.
你的微波炉放在马桶旁边啊
You have a microwave next to your toilet?
你真他妈是天才
You're a genius!
全天下最聪明的吃辣味墨西哥卷的方法
That's the smartest way to eat a burrito.
我考虑周到嘛
I think of everything.
如果你不喜欢你的邻居们
And if you don't like your neighbors,
就可以直接把家推到新的街上去
you push your house to a new street.
或者直接杀了他们
Or you could just kill them
然后把尸体都扔这里面
and throw their bodies in here.
还有个好处  不用租金
Added bonus--no rent.
而且隔壁的中餐馆
And the chinese restaurant next door
还老是把他们的垃圾丢来我屋顶
always tosses their garbage on my roof.
免费外送  爽
Free delivery, yo.
这里不用你介绍
You don't have to tell me.
我在"垃圾箱生活"上有读过了
I read all about this place in "Dumpster Living."
我要了
I'll take it.
行  但随屋附赠一只
All right, but it comes with a very handsome
有着被百货保安怀疑跟踪的发型的
stuffed animal of a man with hair that gets him
超帅气充气玩偶
followed by security at Macy's.
我这么说  不是因为你住在垃圾箱
I'm not just saying this 'cause you live in a dumpster,
但现在
but I'll take some...
我的洞洞想被捅几下
brown chicken, brown cow right now.
所以你在垃圾箱里的"初体验"感觉如何
So what was your first time having sex in a dumpster like?
跟我以前在垃圾箱里的体验很像啊
A lot like the other times I've had sex in a dumpster.
下一次我就会全裸上场
Next time I'm gonna be naked.
下一次我也不会戴着帽子
Next time I won't be wearing this hat.
希望你不要介意
I hope you don't mind.
-但我都这么睡觉  -放开我
- I sleep like this. - Aah! Get off me.
换个活人在我身下的感觉就是好啊
Oh, so nice to have a live body under me for a change.
别弄了  我要被你压扁了
Stop! You're crushing me!
这感觉真好
This is really nice.
是啊
Yeah, it is.
-我走了  -你得走啦
- I got to go. - You got to go?
对啊  我住在餐厅附近那边
Yeah, I live, uh, all the way over by the diner.
而且我还得穿上这些靴子
Plus, I got to pull these boots on.
我还有一匹马和一只猫
And I got a horse and a cat,
还有个可能挂掉的室友  所以...
possibly a dead roommate, so...
懂了  你明天得早起
Right. You got to be up early.
是  但不是你想的那样
Yeah, but not like that.
就只是...
It's just, like--
门把在那里
where's the door handle?
是这个咖啡罐吗
Is it the coffee pot?
我出不去
I can't get out.
我一般出垃圾箱是用爬的
I'm used to climbing out of these things.
就在这里
Ah, it's right here.
你确定你不留下吗
Oh. Sure you don't want to stay?
中餐馆的外卖刚送来了哦
Chinese restaurant just delivered.
那喇叭又响了
There's that horn again.
这绝对跟我们有关
There is no way this is not about us.
麦克斯  又是我
Max, it's me again.
你要是都不接电话
Why do you even have a phone
要手机来干嘛
if you're not gonna pick it up?
还有  你已经是成年人了
And also, you are a grown lady.
为什么你的彩铃是屁声呢
Why is your outgoing message a fart?
我相信你现在正忙着做
And I am sure you're in the middle of
无聊的性爱
having very silly sex,
但家里已经乱成一团
but it is a nightmare around here.
栗宝  南茜跟我都觉得
Chestnut, Nancy, and I are all convinced
那台杀手车在外面打转
that the murder car is still circling
准备把我们全部干掉
and about to take us all out.
她这人真自恋
So self-involved.
这水烧开得也太慢了吧
This water is taking forever to boil.
我现在顶多也只能给杀手们
The best I could do now is offer the killers
在肢解我前  泡上一壶茶
warm tea before they dismember me.
如果你们能听懂  一定觉得好笑
That'd be funny if you got jokes.
两位  计划是这样
Okay, guys, here's the plan.
如果他们走前门  咱们就从后门撤
If they come in that door, we go out this door.
如果他们从后门来  栗宝  你就挡住他们
If they come in that door, Chestnut, you block them,
南茜  你就去抓瞎他们
and, Nancy, you go for their eyes.
算了  大难临头各自飞吧
You know what? Let's just say our good-byes now.
快烧开  快烧开啊
Boil, boil, boil.
没时间了
No time!
门外的人  我手上有锅很烫的水
Whoever you are, I have a pot of pretty hot water!
这堆玩意是怎么回事
What is all this junk?
我的腿  我的美腿啊
My legs! My beautiful legs!
我的脚指沟烫伤了
I burned my toe cleavage.
那是我身上唯一的"沟"呢
And it's the only cleavage I have.
但好歹你的脚趾  看起来的确"大"了
If it helps, your toes do look bigger.
幸好我还有这双拖鞋
Thank God I have these flip-flops
是以前进浴室穿的  后来索性跟你一样不穿了
I used to wear in your shower before I gave up.
你好  我的伤势十万火急
Yes, hi, I have a complete emergency.
我的腿烫伤了
My legs are burned.
好  我明白了
Okay, I hear you.
我帮你排到那个断了腿的男人后面吧
I'll put you right behind the guy whose legs just came off.
谢谢  太感激你了
Thank you. I appreciate that.
我刚才被很烫的水给烫了
See, I just got burned with pretty hot water,
而我很常会穿露脚趾鞋
and I wear a lot of peep-toe shoes.
-健康保险公司是  -用我的奥巴马医保
- Insurance provider? - I'd like to use my Obamacare.
奥巴马医保啊  怎么不早说呢
Oh, Obamacare? Why didn't you say so?
快进来
Come right in.
这态度也变太快了吧
What is the problem?
不是全民都能用奥巴马医保吗
We're all entitled to Obamacare.
电视上的主持人就这么说的
That's what that Rachel Maddow guy said.
我需要更多资料
I'll need more information than that.
密码是  玛利亚
Password, Malia?
你们俩傻逼得先回家  想想你们的健保资料
You clowns need to figure out your insurance information
然后两个小时后再回来
and come back to me in about two hours
而到时我会在沙发上
when I'm on my sofa,
用马克杯喝着威士忌等你们
drinking whiskey out of a coffee mug.
麦克斯  先坐下
Max, let's just sit.
按法律他们一定得让我们就诊
They have to take us, by law.
我以前常抱怨这点  所以我知道
I know because I used to complain about that.
麦克斯你能拿那个流感小册子
Max, can you take that flu season pamphlet
-帮我扇扇脚趾吗  -不要
- and fan my feet? - No.
我才不要碰这里面的任何东西
I'm not touching anything in here,
我从没接打过任何疫苗
'cause I was never vaccinated...
或被疼爱过
or loved.
-谁啊  -是迪克
- Who is it? - It's Deke.
你不接电话吗
You're not gonna answer it?
不要  现在我比较担心你的腿
No, right now, I am very concerned about your legs.
真会撒谎
Aw. You're lying.
你跟迪克怎么了
What happened between you and Deke?
为什么你还会跑回家呢
Why did you even come home tonight?
对"做"得不够好吗
Was the sex bad?
你是不是打他了
Did you hit him?
其实"做"得还行啦
No, the sex was fine.
其实不只是还行
Actually, it was better than fine.
而是超棒  而且我也想留下来过夜
It was great and I wanted to stay.
-所以呢  -所以我立刻走人啦
- So...? - So I left immediately.
麦克斯  别误会我意思
Max, don't take this the wrong way,
但听起来你终于找到了
but it sounds like you found someone
一位能让你开心的人
who finally makes you happy
但你却故意破坏这段感情
and you're trying to ruin it.
原来我的感觉是这么回事
Oh, that's what this feeling is.
-我得抽离这段感情  -为什么
- Well, I got to get rid of it. - Why?
我从小就被培养成不开心的人
I wasn't raised to be happy.
我从小就被灌输罐装肉就是最好的肉
I was raised to believe canned meat is as good as it gets.
厄尔  我的腿被热水烫伤了
Earl, I spilled hot water on my feet.
你绝对想象不到我正承受着多大痛苦
You can't imagine how much pain I'm in.
我把自己关在一家7-11的厕所里
Well, I kicked heroin in a 7/11 bathroom
戒了三天的毒
for three days.
但你的脚趾被烫到  真是太可怜了
But sorry about your burnt tootsies though.
卡洛琳  抱歉没回你短信
Caroline, sorry I didn't text you back.
本来我昨晚愿意过去你家的
I would've come over last night,
但我"第二人生"里的老婆生了孩子
but my Second Life wife had a baby.
我真不敢相信
I just can't believe you had
九个月前你就跟人假做爱了  却一直保密到现在
fake sex nine months ago and didn't tell anyone.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
我想找在这里工作的金发瘦妞
I'm looking for a skinny blonde that works here.
她死了
Uh... She died.
-她就在那边  -她复活了
- She right over there. - Ooh, she came back to life!
赞美上帝
Hallelujah!
我有东西要给你
Hey, I got something for you.
不要啊
No!
-是自制专辑  -不要啊
- It's a mix tape. - No!
我特别为你制作的
I made it for you.
我兄弟拿小蛋糕丢你真是对不起
I'm sorry my brother threw that cupcake at you.
他对谷蛋白过敏  所以闹脾气
He's gluten-free and upset about it.
我有机会带你出去约会吗
So can I take you out sometime?
你这番举动很贴心  你也像是好人
Uh... uh, very sweet, and you seem great,
但我已经跟一个戴红头巾的人
but I'm already in a relationship
在一起了
with a guy in a red bandana.
没关系  我就问问
No worries. Just thought I'd ask.
你刚才干嘛了
What did you just do?
永远不要拒绝车窗贴黑的男人
You never say no to a guy with tinted windows.
这是天字第二号规矩
That's rule number two.
他的电话在上面  我随时可以找他啊
Well, his number's on here. I can always call him back.
然后我们就可以一起跟
Then we can both be in relationships
不喜欢的人处对象了
we don't want to be in.
-什么对象  -迪克啊
- Relationship? - Deke.
你明天就会在学校见到他
You're gonna see him at pastry school tomorrow.
他肯定想知道被甩的原因
He's gonna wanna know.
男人从来不想知道
Guys never wanna know.
他们死都不想知道原因
In fact, they are dying not to know.
麦克斯  为啥你昨晚要走
Max, why'd you leave last night?
我想知道原因
I wanna know.
你昨晚本来都已经是"捅捅捅  谢赏炮"
I mean, you were all like, "Wham-bam, thank you, man."
我的脑子刚才也在说"千万别说
And yeah, my brain was like, "Don't say it,
绝对别说  千万别说"
don't say it, don't say it, don't say it,"
但我还是问了
but I said it.
到底怎么回事
What's going on?
做爱做得太差劲了
Uh... The sex was bad.
那你在我背上留的抓痕是怎么回事
What about the scratches on my back?
我是想挣脱
I was trying to get away.
我就不当电灯泡了
I'll just leave you two alone.
我就在一边看看我的自制专辑吧
I'll just be over here, looking at my mix tape.
第一首歌  "淫荡点"
Oh, track one, "Make It Nasty."
你说得对  麦克斯
You're right, Max.
昨晚做爱超差劲  超不爽
The sex was bad, really bad.
我们做第二次的时候又更差劲
And it was worse when we did it the second time.
而第三次简直就是场灾难
And that third time was a disaster.
我只坚持了47分钟而已  而你尖叫个屁啊
I mean, I only lasted 47 minutes, and you screamed.
忍痛走远点也比不上
Okay, walking away has to be
听这对话来得难受
less painful than hearing this.
不用  卡洛琳  我跟她去外面谈
No, stay, Caroline. We'll go outside.
麦克斯  跟我来
Max, come with me for a second.
我想让你看个东西
I wanna show you something.
直接"放鸟"出来吧
Just whip it out here.
反正你也不会是今晚这里第一个露鸟的人
You wouldn't be the first guy to do that tonight.
也不会是最后一个
Nor will he be the last.
你到底想让我看什么
Okay, what do you wanna show me?
那是你的垃圾箱之家吗
Is that your dumpster?
你说你不能留下是因为
Look, you said you couldn't stay over
餐厅离我那太远了
because you lived all the way over by the diner,
所以我就把它拖过来
so I moved it here to figure out
看看你下次要用什么借口
what your next excuse would be.
我有种族歧视
Um, I'm racist.
我也是  白人女最事儿精了
Yeah, me too. White girls are a hassle.
还有呢
What else?
你的衣服上有鸟图案
You have a bird on your shirt.
你明明很爱
You love it.
的确
I do.
还有吗
What else?
-想不出了  -非常好
- I got nothin'. - Good.
所以何不
So what do you say
别再像个白痴一样
you stop being such a stupid face,
赶紧带着你性感屁屁
and get your sweet dumper
爬进我的垃圾箱吧
into my dumpster right now,
"棕鸡"跟"棕牛"正耐心地
where a brown chicken and a brown cow
在里面等着跟你啪啪啪呢
are waiting patiently for you.
听好
Look.
如果你想要我进那垃圾箱
If you want me in that dumpster,
你就得用传统的方法带我进去
you'll have to get me there the traditional way.
胶带捆我手腕
Duct tape my wrists,
布袋盖我头  然后扔我进去
throw a bag over my head, and toss me in.
-很不给力吧  -太差了
- Awful, huh? - So bad.
想等会再来一发
Want to do it again later,
然后在这过夜  然后再来一发吗
and then sleep over tonight, and then do it again?
好啊
Sure.
我们能有光着身子"做"的机会吗
Are we ever gonna do it naked?
等你搬进一个有足够空间
Yeah, when you move into a place
让我的巨臀出鞘的地方吧
big enough for me to take my pants off.
我得先警告你
Look, I got to warn you.
我不知道怎么开心
I don't know how to be happy.
那你脸上为什么有这么大的笑容
Then why do you have that big smile on your face?
那是假笑
I'm faking it.
为什么床还在摇  我们还在做爱吗
Why is it shaking? Are we still having sex?
谢谢你了  也请好好享用小蛋糕
Thank you, sir. Enjoy your cupcake.
麦克斯
Max?
别拖走我们啊  这是迪克的家
Don't tow us. This is Deke's house.
他住在垃圾箱里吗
He lives in a dumpster?
是啊  但他是故意的
Yeah, but on purpose.
你今晚还是会回家的  对吧
But you're coming home tonight, right?
麦克斯  麦克斯
Max, Max!
阿憨
Han?
阿憨  你今晚有空吗
Han, what are you doing tonight?